Translated by Releska
I wish to have a chance in the future
And I will always be with you
What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up
If I have no hope in this world, I will be with you
I'm so happy that I won't be with you
Even if I have to go, I'm not allowed to fall for it
There's a smile on your lips
With you, with you, with you
If you love me,
I'll be with you for a long time
I don't want to be with you
Are you ready?
If we were to experiment with Tom Machine,
It would have been great!
We had a lot of fun in the world!
I don't even know where to go,
I don't even know how to go back to the world
But it's not the first time I've ever been in a world
I'm happy to be with my younger brother's family
I'm happy to be with my younger brother
I'm happy to be with you
I'm happy to be with my younger brother's family
Hey, we're not doing something bad
We're not doing something bad
Why?
That's why we have to do something to change the world
I don't know what's going on in the future
First, let's get started
Let's go!
I don't think it's difficult
Yeah
I always get it
Let's do it
What is this?
Isn't this a sign?
It's a sign
Hey, it's a sign
Hey, please
Let's get started
Huh?
What happened?
It's starting
Did you get sick?
It's starting to look like this
Can't you open it?
It's starting
Nero, what did you get?
I got it
Hey, you heard it
It's a curse of practice
Nero
It's a curse of love
It's a curse of the second, but it's a curse of love
People are talking so much
Change it
If you're going to cry, it's a curse
That's why
The person you are looking for is a curse of love
It's a curse of love
You...
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong?
You're not in a good mood?
You're a little girl, aren't you?
That's why you're looking for a curse of love
It's a curse of love
Don't come to my house
I'll put it on the window
That's right
I want to get a picture of you as usual.
Hmm, I see.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's finally ready to be fried for the next bite, right?
Honey, honey.
I'm smoking,
so let's have it deliciously.
Honey!
Honey...
It's so delicious!
Mom.
I don't need to explain.
I've never heard of this.
I thought it was a real hot dog.
You think I'm a good boy?
You don't have a horse, right?
I'm a straightforward old man.
You look like a hot dog.
I always put on a headband,
and set up an all-time job.
This is all I can do.
I only do this at the dentist.
And this is all I can do,
and that's all I can do.
In the meantime, I'm going to ride on my own.
That's great.
Oh! What are you doing?
I'm going!
Well, if you do this, you won't be able to make a lot of money, right?
I won't do anything like that!
Oh, I see!
Hey!
Come on!
Come on, come on!
Hey, look!
Hey!
I can't go from here!
Hey, don't do that!
Hey!
You two, too!
Hey, hey!
I've finally lost!
I won't let you go anymore!
You really don't have to lose, right?
Yeah!
That's not the difference!
I've been doing it all by myself!
I'm glad!
I've finally lost!
I've finally lost.
I'm happy, but I've finally lost so much for tonight!
Not only is he just going to eat food, but he doesn't have to.
He hasn't even eaten food yet!
He has only eaten food yet.
We're going to eat飽 with the milk and take it to Durand.
Hey!
What do I do after all?
Hey, Mom and me!
I know you have a good habit of yours.
If you eat so tightly, you'll want to eat more.
You don't look like a good girl.
You're just a little bit older.
Tenba!
It's falling!
Oh, I'm going to become a little boy!
I'm going to destroy your power by chasing two girls!
Shut up, you little girl!
Hey!
No!
You're going to go home!
Yeah!
Hey!
Look!
The inside is beautiful, right?
Beautiful, beautiful!
Beautiful!
Hey!
Let's eat!
Thank you!
Look!
You're eating too?
Thank you!
Mmm!
It's good!
You're eating too!
Where are you going?
I'm not going to eat too!
Thank you!
Yeah!
I'm going to show you what it's called in front of my child!
It's not that good, right?
Beautiful, beautiful!
Beautiful!
Yeah!
What's wrong with you?
Did something happen to you?
Beautiful!
No!
Hey!
If we look at the inside of the garden,
it looks like it looks cute!
Why don't you tell us if you know how to do this?
I don't want to.
Rock?
Oh!
Hey!
I won't let you go until you get it from the first place.
Rock!
You got the same pattern as my master.
How about a little thing?
You did a small thing and you're getting it all in?
You put in all of it!?
Rock, rock!
Are you a fool?
Rock, rock, rock, rock, rock!
I'm good at it now, Rock.
Well, I'm a fool at all.
But, this time, it's the justice of the Dataji Rock.
What the hell is that?
There's something wrong with the Dataji Rock!
I'm going to die!
What's going on?
I'm not going to let you go!
Besides, you're a little bit tired, Rock.
But I'm sure you're going to be tired.
Well, since it's the battle of the KBQ,
I'm sure you're tired, Rock.
I'm sure you're not going to let me go.
I see.
Well, it's been a long time since I've been worried about Nika and Ryo-shi.
I've never seen Nika and Ryo-shi see each other.
It's been a long time since I've seen Nika and Ryo-shi see each other.
I'm going to hide my truth from you.
Is it true?
I can't talk to you all this much, 6.
That's right!
Good, but I can't...
What's going on?
Is it a proposal for the flowers?
No, Manchikun.
That's the future.
The future, the future, and the future.
That day, Mr. Goji was present to Mr. Goji's flowers.
Well, then, Mr. Goji's wedding anniversary is about to begin.
That's a good story.
This year, Mr. Goji forgot about Mr. Goji's flowers.
What?
That's why, Mr. Goji's flowers.
But Mr. Goji was a normal family.
That's true, Mr. Goji.
I think he's quite a good boy.
Mr. Goji, I'm worried about whether the flowers will grow up.
Is it okay to put them on?
I think it's okay to put them on the flowers.
I said, the flowers won't grow up, and Mr. Goji's flowers will grow up.
It's time to get on the way.
The flowers will grow up, Mr. Goji.
Mr. Goji, I said, the flowers will grow up.
Yes, this is the flowers that will grow up.
Goji, goji!
I'm not worried about it.
I made a sword sword, but Mr. Goji's flowers.
I forgot about Mr. Goji's flowers.
That's right.
The flowers will grow up, and the flowers will grow up.
It's still a long time.
The flowers are growing up, Mr. Goji.
That's right.
Good.
Good. Good. Good.
Mr. Goji, good.
But Mr. Goji's flowers are growing up, Mr. Goji.
I don't think that's the right way to put them on.
That's what I think.
Good. Good. Good.
But Mr. Goji's flowers are growing up, Mr. Goji.
The flowers are growing up, Mr. Goji.
Good. Good.
What should we do?
That's right.
We didn't do anything about the sword.
Hey, Mr. Goji.
That's right.
Good.
I'm sorry.
That's right. That's right.
That's right.
What should we do?
We can't listen to the sound of the sky.
Think about it.
Hey, hey.
Don't talk about it.
What?
Hey, hey.
Mr. Goji's flowers are growing up, Mr. Goji.
Huh?
He used to propose to the fairy tale doctor,
but the fairy tale has a different point for both.
The fairy tale has a different point of the time
that the fairy tale was the first to arrive.
But there's a different point for both.
Really?
The day we get closer,
it's not as hard as the time seems.
That's right.
The fairy tale is quite different.
It's a bit of a disanction, isn't it?
And then, the present of the teacher is
a time-to-time special.
Time-to-time special?
Something like that.
Well, I don't know where to do it.
That's true.
If you go to the wrong place, it's okay.
Hey!
I'm so sick.
Hey, hey!
What's up?
I was worried about the air.
That's it! It's the first time you've been here.
Yeah.
Let's go, let's go.
Everyone, let's go to the train station?
Yeah! Let's go!
Zeta, wake up!
It's too hot!
If you're free, you're free!
What's up, Nika?
What's up? You're free to eat, right?
Nika, Nika, you're free!
Zeta, wake up!
Nika, Nika, wake up!
Nika, Nika!
Zeta, Zeta...
What's up, Nika?
It's too hot, Nika!
Gochiyori, you're here!
It's too hot.
Zeta, Zeta...
Nika, Nika...
Koji, Koji, you're free!
You're free to eat, right?
Nika...
It was a dangerous place, Nika.
Nika, are you all right?
I'm fine, Koji.
Koji, Koji, you're here, too.
Nika, Nika...
Koji, you're the only one in the world, Koji.
Nika...
This is a different place, Koji.
Koji, Koji, you're the only one in the world, Koji.
Koji...
It doesn't look like it's time.
This is different, Koji.
What's up?
You're the only one in the world.
That's it, huh?
I'm the only one in the world.
Koji...
What's up?
I'm going to do it.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'll give you two more.
Run, Agama!
Run!
It's a bad guy.
you are angering us.
If, we must also try to answer Mygan knee.
I need to try his knee.
No, I should try his knee.
Kojita, you are a problem with asking off my proper daily life.
It's not enough.
Run.
See!Give me your knee.
I'm going to get you.
I'm not going to get you.
I'm not going to get you!
I wonder if I can get you a little bit more.
I did it!
Did you see that?
Today is the day of Naganauri.
Everyone is looking forward to it.
The party of Kuropozukinenbi is here.
Kuropozukinenbi.
I like you.
But I like you very much.
Yes, I'm going to the party.
I'm going to the party.
Huh?
Oh, it's good.
I think this is one of the three of us.
I don't like it, but I'm interested in it.
It's really good.
That's right.
This is the party of Kuropozukinenbi.
I won't let you go this time.
Nike Nika-chan.
Let's put your finger on it.
Nika!
Eh?
It turned out to be a little uncomfortable.
Is it okay for you?
Nika!
The End
It's a big deal!
Well, I can't use this world...
Uyaa! Uya! Uya! Uya!
Huh?
I'm riding a Dumbo!
It's so easy!
Let's go!
Huh?
The sound of something strange!
I heard somewhere!
The End
Next time, we'll be together!
We'll be together!
Uya! Uya!